# MEET UPADHYAY

Jhapatapur, Kharagpur, 721301 phone: (+91) 9635187666 email: meetupadhyaykgp@gmail.com

### Work Experience

Software Developer (June 2021 - July 2022)

Worked as a software developer in TCS in a migration project for 6 months. In which worked on python (3.7 version) and PostgreSQL. (Client: GE, Project name: One wind).

Worked as a software developer in TCS in a migration project for 5 months. In which worked on NodeJS, STS (Java 1.8), and PostgreSQL. (Client: GE, Project name: HPCi EMPC).

Analyst (August 2022- Now)

Working as a Analyst at Axtria- Ingenious Insights.

#### Education

B.Tech (2017 - 2021)

Institute: Gandhi Institute for Technological Advancement

Board: BPUT

CGPA: 8.76

Higher Secondary (2015 – 2017)

Institute: Kendriya Vidyalaya AFS Salua

Board: CBSE

CGPA: 9.3

Secondary (2014 – 2015)

Institute: Kendriya Vidyalaya AFS Salua

Board: CBSE CGPA: 9.8

## **Projects**

- Personal Assistant (MAYA) using Python.
- TODO List using Flask API and SQL Lite as database deployed using heroku.
- Personal Blog Using Flask and MySQL as database.

#### Profile

Software Developer with industry experience and hands on experience in Python, C++, Flask, MySQL, Java, HTML, CSS and Bootstrap. Excellent listening and communication skills and able to adapt and improvise according to the job role. Experienced in working with team and delivering the task before deadline.

## Languages

- Python:
- Flask:
- C++:
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap:
- MySQL:
- Java:
- React JS:

### Tools and IDE

- VScode and Pycharm
- Spring Tool Suite
- Sonar: Quality check
- GitHub: Git (Push, Pull, Clone etc.)
- Rally: User story creation and maintenance
- Postman, Putty, WinSCP